铁血战士大战异形2
好了,慢慢来
Okay, now, take your time
可以了
There you go
爸爸,爸爸,在上面
Dad! Dad! It's up here!
慢点,山姆,慢点
Slow down, Sam, slow down
哇
Wow...
是啊,我们,我们得去通知警长
Yeah, we're...we're gonna show this to the sheriff
怎么回事? 好了,我们走
What's happening? Come on, let's go
快点,走
Come on...go!
快点,跑,跑,跑
Move it. Go, go, go!
快点,山姆
Go, Sam...
山姆,你没事吧?
Sam, you all right?
低头
Stay down
爸爸,我害怕
Dad, I'm scared
小心
Watch out!
爸爸
Dad
爸爸?
Dad...?
还好吧,达拉斯?
How you doin', Dallas?
艾迪
Eddie
好啦,我带你一段吧
Come on, I'll give you a ride
我以前都是坐在后面的
Yeah, I usually ride in the back
我记得有几次
I seem to remember you being with me
也是你在前面开车吧
a couple of those times
能问你点东西?
Ask you something?
你,呃,你后悔吗?
You, uh...You regret what you did?
不
No
怎么了,你觉得我应该后悔?
Why? You thought I would?
我只是觉得三年该够长了
I think three years is a long time
怎么? 你在雇人?
You got work lined up?
你找到工作了吗?
Why? You hiring?
我说服别人够麻烦的了
I've got enough trouble convincing people
这是我的工作
I belong on the job
不过,我愿意跑遍整个镇子来找你
But I'll ask around town for you
我很感激
I appreciate it
你,见到我弟弟了吗?
You, uh...seen my brother?
实际上,我见他见得都烦了
Actually, I been seeing him too much
大佬比萨店,需要点什么吗?
Pizza One. How can I help you?
记得带帽子
Gotta wear the hat
祖,你让我们带帽子
Drew, the only reason you make us wear a hat
仅仅是因为当你以前当司机的时候
is 'cause some manager made you wear a hat
某些经理要求你带帽子
when you were a driver
听着,你能得到这份工作
Look, the only reason you got this job
仅仅是因为你的监护顾问
is because your guidance counselor begged me
求着我给你的
to give it to you
是啊,我知道她的性感
Yeah, I'm sure the fact that she's hot
跟这没有一点关系,对吧?
had nothing to do with that, huh?
水冠街1427号
1427 Watercrest
我不能送这个货
I can't make that delivery
让白瑞去送吧
Have Barry do it
这里不讲民主
This is not a democracy
要么送过去,要么走人
Make the run or you're fired
记得带帽子
And wear the hat!
巡逻31号大卫报告
This is R-31-David
正在对4号下水道枢纽例行检查
investigating a 10-66 at sewer junction four
收到,巡逻31号大卫
Copy that, R-31-David
哈瑞,跟你说过多少次了,叫你这些人不要到这儿来
Harry...we keep telling you guys to stay out of here...
你却老跑回来
and you keep coming back
我不想这样做,不过我必须得把你带回去
I hate to do this, but I'm gonna have to take you in
让我找找我的狗吧
Let me just get my dog
布斥?
Butch?
布斥
Butch!
过来,孩子
Come here, boy
这是什么?
What is that?
天呐
Jesus!
警长,警长
Uh...Sheriff, Sheriff...
嗨,瑞奇
Hey, Ricky
嗨,杰西
Hi, Jesse
进来吧
Come on in
我给你拿点喝的?
Can I get you something to drink?
不用了,谢谢
I'm good, thanks
装备不错啊,瑞奇
That's a cute outfit, Ricky
是啊,是不是圣诞提前到了?
Yeah, isn't Halloween in October?
至少我知道谁订了"腊肠情人"
At least now I know who ordered the "Sausage Lover's."
哦
Ooh!
我的钱包在厨房里
My purse is in the kitchen
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
他真是个混蛋
He can be such an asshole
是啊,没错,你一直都知道怎么结交他们
Yeah, well...you've always known how to pick 'em, Jess
我可以告诉你个小秘密
Well, I'll let you in on a little secret:
我准备解雇他了
I'm getting ready to fire him
解雇他
Fire him
很有趣
That's funny
我要付你多少钱?
So what do I owe you?
恩,53.50圆
Uh...$53.50
别找了
Keep it
谢谢
Thanks
等会见
I'll see you later
来啊
Come on!
戴尔,戴尔,住手
Dale! Dale, stop it!
就为了一个微笑,值得吗?
Was that laugh you got worth it?
不回答?
Huh? No answer?
戴尔,让他走
Dale, leave him alone!
把钥匙给我
Give me my keys
看看你能不能在30分钟内,找到钥匙,傻B
If you can find 'em in 30 minutes or less, asshole
走
Let's go
婊子
Bitch
比萨小子
Pizza boy
回家,杰西
Let's go, Jesse!
试着发现更多的信息
...try and get more information
找到可能的伤员,并且报告是否需要救护车
and call about possible injuries and whether medical is needed
救护车,死者,(美国警方无线电用语)
14-29
雷,你发现了什么?
Ray, you find anything?
没有
Nothing
有人把车停在岔路口吗?
Anyone parked at the turnout?
巴迪·本森的卡车
Buddy Benson's truck
天呐,艾迪
Jesus, Eddie
他一般都和孩子一起出来的
He usually goes out with his kid
爸爸?
Dad?
嘿
Hey!
我真想你
I missed you so much
她长这么大了
She's so big!
是啊
I know
嘿
Hey!
上帝,我真不敢相信你回来了
God. I can't believe you're home!
好久了
It's been so long
要我帮你吗?
You want some help?
这些是给我的?
Are these for me?
你不喜欢?
You don't like them?
什么,你开玩笑吗?
What, are you kidding me?
这么酷
Those are so cool
等会我们来教你怎么用,好吗?
We'll show you how they work later, okay?
好吧
Okay
好了
All right
好
你的门有问题吗?
You got a problem with the door?
你什么时候回来的?
When'd you get back?
今天
Today
你的脸怎么了?
What happened to your face?
等会儿再谈
Talk about it later
瑞奇
Ricky...
- 嘿 - 我们等会儿再谈
- Hey!      - We'll talk about it later
- 我们现在就谈 - 把手拿开
- Let's talk about it now      - Get your hands off
把你该死的手拿开
Get your fuckin' hands off me!
你的脸到底怎么了?
What happened to your face?
戴尔·科林斯和他的朋友打了我
Dale Collins and his friends jumped me
还把我的钥匙扔进下水道
They threw my keys in the sewer
好吧,把球棒给我
All right, give me the bat
你在这里干什么?
- What are you doing here...      - Ricky...
- 你要干什么? - 我不会再说一遍
- What are you doing? !      - I'm not gonna ask...
把那该死的球棒给我
Give me the fuckin' bat
好啦,我帮你去找钥匙
Come on...I'll help you find your keys
布斥,闭嘴
Butch, shut up!
哈瑞?
Harry?
最好给我留点
Better save some for me
哦,老天啊
Oh, my God
哦,哈瑞
Oh, Harry
救命
Please!
妈妈
Mom!
很抱歉,你该睡了,甜心
I'm sorry. It's your bedtime, honey
我还不困呢
I'm not sleepy yet
茉莉
Molly
把它放到一边
Put those away
该睡觉了
It's time for bed
我爱你
I love you
我想让爸爸读
I want Dad to read it
好吧
Okay
我爱你
I love you
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning
好吗?
Okay?
嘿
Hey...
你记得多少次
You remember all those times
你跟我说你很想念妈妈?
you told me how much you missed Mommy?
告诉她,没关系的
It's okay to tell Mommy that
好的
Okay
嘿
Hey
你把她照顾得很好
You've done an amazing job with her
她一直很想你
She's missed you
我离开,她生我气
She's angry that I left
茉莉只是需要点时间
Well, Molly just needs a little time
也许我犯了个错误
Maybe I made a mistake
没有,你没有犯错
Hey, no. You didn't make a mistake
我们只是很想念你
We've just missed you
我也很想你们,真的
I missed you too. Yeah
快点
Hurry up
你想自己来?
You want to do it?
你是家里的罪人
You're the convict in the family
好笑
Funny
帮我一下,好吗?
Help me out, all right?
为什么我们不从
Why don't we just climb down
他们扔钥匙的地方爬下去?
from where they threw your keys?
那样杰西就可以看到我满身是屎地爬出来?
So Jesse can see me climb out covered in shit?
不,谢谢
No, thanks
等一下
Wait a second
我们会满身是屎?
We're gonna be covered in shit?
拿着
Take this
这下面真恶心
It's gross down here
我能想出更恶心的地方
I can think of worse places
我猜没人在家
Guess nobody's home
那是个睡椅吗?
Is that a couch?
是的
Yeah
比咱家的好
It's nicer than ours
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
哦,闻起来像有东西死在这里了
Oh, it smells like something died down here
你确定是这条路?
You sure this is the right way?
应该就在那上边(水冠街,1400-1500区)
This should be it right up here
就是这个下水道
That's the drain
检查下
Check down there
是你的钥匙,混蛋
They're your keys, asshole
你有手
You got hands
是,不过我可不打算把手叉到那堆屎里,你自己捞
Yeah, and I'm not sticking 'em in that shit. You do it
怪你自己吧
Knock yourself out
跟我说说这个女孩
Tell me about this girl
哪个女孩?
What girl?
让你屁股挨揍的女孩
The one you got your ass kicked over
就只是个女孩
It's just a girl
没人只是为了个一般女孩
No one goes digging around through shit
在屎里面挖东西
over just some girl
好吗?
Okay?
那他妈是什么玩意?
What the hell was that?
放松,就是只老鼠
Relax. It's just a rat
那他妈才不是老鼠
It's no fuckin' rat
好了,检查下那个下水道
All right, check that drain
我找到了
I got 'em
走吧
Let's go
妈的,警长,巴迪的老婆来了
Shit, Sheriff. That's Buddy's wife
嘿,我们有伴儿了
Hey, we got some company
- 达西 - 艾迪
- Darcy      - Eddie
我没收到任何消息
I haven't heard anything
- 我们正在找他们 - 他们可能受伤了
- We're looking for them      - They could be hurt
他们也可能正在回家的路上
Or they could be on their way home
你在浪费时间
You're wasting your time
好了,伙计们,请回到你的车里去
Okay, folks, please, go back and get in your cars
艾迪,我的家人在里面
Eddie, my family is out there
我们会找到他们的,交给我们吧
And we're gonna find them. Let us handle it
今天晚上你们去寻找,太危险了
It's too dangerous out there for you all to search tonight
现在开始,我们自己负责了,警长
Around here, we take care of our own, Sheriff
不管有没有你们,我们都会去找的
We're gonna do the search whether you like it or not
山姆?
Sam?
雷,往桥那边走
Ray, head towards the bridge
山姆,你在哪儿?
Sammy, where are you? !
巴迪
Buddy? !
巴迪?
山姆
Sam? !
凯莉,把他们带过来
Kelly, bring 'em in!
你在哪儿,巴迪?
Where are you, Buddy?
山姆? 山姆?
Sam? Sam?
巴迪,巴迪
Buddy! Buddy!
巴迪
Buddy!
我们不会扔下你不管的,山姆
We won't stop looking for you, Sammy!
艾迪?
Eddie?
达西,我们明天再来找
Darcy, we'll start up again tomorrow
我的丈夫和孩子就在里面,某个地方
My husband and my son are out here...somewhere
他们不会扔下我不管的
They wouldn't stop looking for me
你觉得是不是
Do you think that...
发生了什么?
something happened?
我不知道
I don't know
你为什么不回家去,休息一下?
Why don't you go home and get some rest?
走吧,我们需要你的力量
Come on, we need your strength
好吧
Right
我们明天早上集合
We're going to regroup tomorrow in the morning
在晚上找没什么用
We're no good at night here
雷,有发现吗?
Ray, anything?
没有
Negative
我将最后一次检查大桥那边
I'm gonna make a final pass by the ridge
好的,保持联系
All right, keep in touch
还有,我明天早上再找你
Otherwise, I'll see you in the morning
所有单位,报告情况
All units, report back
请原谅,先生
Excuse me, sir
如果你见到了我丈夫和儿子
If you've seen my husband or my son...
- 好的 - 谢谢你
- Okay      - Thank you
请原谅
Pardon me
请看看这个
If I could give you this
这是我的丈夫和孩子
This is my husband and my son
请留意一下
Just keep an eye
- 当然 - 谢谢你们
- Oh, sure      - Thank you
吉那森小镇因为最近
Gunnison residents have been jolted
一个男子和他孩子的神秘失踪而震动
by the mysterious disappearance of a man and his young son
在昨天的搜救过程中
during a hunting trip yesterday
巴迪·本森,吉那森镇
Buddy Benson, a repair supervisor
电信公司的高级工程师
for the Gunnison telephone company
还有他的儿子,山姆,并没有回家
and his young son, Sam, never returned home last night
茉莉? 宝贝,过来吃
Molly? Honey, come eat
工作找的怎么样了?
How's the job hunt going?
破门而入算不算特长?
Is breaking and entering a special skill?
你有什么建议吗?
You got any suggestions?
我听说银行在招人
I hear the bank's hiring
早啊,警长
Morning, Sheriff
嘿
Hey
早
Morning
巴迪和他的儿子有消息了吗?
Any word on Buddy and his kid?
凯瑞?
Carrie?
请倒点咖啡
Coffee, please
你们整晚都在找?
You guys have been out all night, huh?
没有,我们两点就停下了
No. We called it off at 2:00 a.m
雷没有回家?
Ray didn't come home?
艾迪,我以为他跟着你
Eddie, I thought he was out with you
我打过他的手机
I tried his cell phone
凯瑞,听我说
Carrie, listen to me
雷昨天晚上很着急
Ray was pushing real hard last night
我肯定他还在找
I'm sure he's still looking
监狱管理那边
Cell reception out there...
他平时都会打的,艾迪
He always calls, Eddie
雷
Ray!
Ray? !
雷,你在那边吗?
Ray, you down there?
雷?
Ray?
哦,老天啊
Oh, my God
我不相信这是,雷·亚当姆斯
I can't believe this is Ray Adams
我也不想相信
I don't want to believe it either
知道什么能驱使一个人这么干?
Know what it would take for a man to do this?
让一个人,活活剥别人的皮?
For someone to...skin a human being?
没有一点痕迹
There were no tracks
没有
Nothing
艾迪,这次太麻烦了
Eddie, you're in over your head
你打算怎么做?
What are you going to do?
我想出来后,会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I figure it out
嘿
Hey
嘿,杰西
Hey, Jesse
嗨
Hi
知道吗,在教室你就是用这种眼神看我的
You know, you look at me that same way in class
是啊,啊,嗯
Yeah, well, uh...
钟表在你背后
the clock's behind you
什么?
What?
明天你去上课的时候,回头
Tomorrow when you are in class, turn around
你就能看到
You'll see it
是啊,我
Yeah, I...
我知道钟在那儿,不过
I know that it's there, but...
我们都知道,你看的不是钟
we both know that's not what you're looking at
知道吗,你一直不善于说谎
You know, you never were a good liar
今晚,你想去游泳吗?
Do you want to go swimming tonight?
游泳
Swimming
在哪儿?
Where?
学校
At school
来吧,就跟过去一样
Come on, it'll be like old times
过去,在你有男朋友之前?
Old times like before you had a boyfriend?
是的
Yeah
不过,实际上,是前男友
And it's ex-boyfriend, actually
他被解雇了
He's been fired
那么,今晚?
So, tonight
10点左右
Around 10:00
晚上见
See you tonight
我们正在关门,达西
We're closing out now, Darcy
等你过来再见了
See you when you get here
你没事吧
You all right?
如果你想谈谈
If you want to talk...
没事
It's okay
今晚你可以跟我还有凯西住在一起
You're welcome to stay with me and Cathy tonight
达西正在赶过来,我跟她一起住
Darcy's coming by... I'm gonna stay with her
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow
我们在树林里找到了雷的尸体
We found Ray's body in the woods
他,嗯,他被活活剥了皮
He was, uh...he was skinned alive
你觉得这跟
Think it's got something to do with...
巴迪和他的孩子的失踪有关?
Buddy and his kid disappearing?
我觉得这种事从来没发生过
I think this kind of thing doesn't happen here
你告诉他妻子了?
You told his wife?
警长,我们收到报告说
Sheriff, we have a report
16区下水道有小规模煤气爆炸
of a small gas explosion in the sewer under 16th
- 你收到了吗? - 明白,分派员
- Do you copy?      - Roger, Dispatch
通知消防队,我们在那儿跟他们汇合
- Notify the fire department      - I'll meet 'em there
马上,警长,分派员结束通话
Right away, Sheriff. Dispatch out
你需要帮忙吗?
You want some help?
我不知道,达拉斯
I don't know, Dallas
来吧
Come on
我坐到后面
I'll ride in the back
内特?
Nate?
Nate? !
内特,你跑哪儿去了?
Nate, where are you?
什么?
What?
瑞奇
Ricky
嘿
Hey
那么,呃
So, uh...
我们怎么进去?
how do we get in?
放学后我复制了钥匙
I taped the lock after class
我不能决定该穿哪件泳衣,所以
I couldn't decide on which suit I wanted to wear, so...
现在,你告诉我
Now...you tell me...
你看的是我,还是钟?
...are you looking at me or the clock?
过来
Come here
哦,天啊
Oh, my God
你觉得你在做什么,杰丝?
What do you think you're doing, Jess?
戴尔,滚出去
Dale, get out of here
记住我的话,瑞奇
Just remember, Ricky...
这个小婊子知道每件事,都是我教的
I taught this little slut everything she knows
- 不,瑞奇 - 住手
No, Ricky...stop it!
住手,戴尔,住手
Stop it! Dale, stop it!
住手,他会淹死的
Stop it! He's drowning!
放开我
Get off me
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
哦,上帝
Oh, my God
上帝,赶快从水里出来
Oh, my God, get out of the water
- 出去 - 杰西,跑
- Get out!      - Jesse, go!
跑
Go!
哦,上帝,从水池里出来
Oh, my God, get out of the pool!
杰丝,跑
Jess, run!
哦,天呐
Oh, my God!
跑,跑
Go! Go!
你觉得他死了吗?
Do you think he's dead?
你为什么不回去看看?
Why don't you go back and find out?
不
No
这边
Here!
窗户
Window!
妈的,妈的
Shit! Oh, shit!
啊,救救我
Aah, help me!
加油
Come on!
救命,啊
Help me, aah!
瑞奇,快走
Ricky, come on!
走
Go!
警长,核电站发生了一起爆炸
Sheriff we have a 10-80 at the nuclear power plant
收到,我们在十分钟后赶到
Roger that. We'll be there in 10 minutes
好的,警长,国家安全局也被通知到了
10-4, Sheriff. County and state have been advised as well
打算告诉我发生了什么吗?
Wanna tell me what the hell's goin' on?
核电站发生了一起爆炸
There's been an explosion at the plant
今天变的更有意思了
Well, this day keeps getting better
爸爸,爸爸
Daddy, Daddy!
- 爸爸 - 嘿
- Daddy!      - Hey
怎么了?
What is it?
那东西在外面
It was outside the window
什么?
What?
一个怪物
It was a monster
哦,到这来
Oh, come here
过来
Come here
知道吗,我像你这么大的时候
You know, when I was your age...
我也经常做这种噩梦
I used to have these awful nightmares
我看到了
I saw it
是真的
It was real
看,没有怪物
See? No monster
蒂姆
Tim!
爸爸
Daddy!
Dad!
我们得跑
We have to go
快点
Come on!
爸爸
Daddy!
大火吞噬了整个核电站
The fire spread through the whole plant
他们必须手动关闭核反应装置
They have to shut down the reactors manually
收到
Roger that
分派员,我们得疏散整个镇
Dispatch, we have to evacuate the entire town
请求科罗拉多州国民警卫队援助
Call the National Guard in Colorado Springs for assistance
完毕
Over
好的
10-4
上帝啊
Jesus Christ
- 警长 - 是
- Sheriff      - Yeah
你得来听听这个
I think you should hear about this
达拉斯
Dallas!
好吧,非常感谢
All right, thanks a lot
瑞奇,你跑到这个鬼地方干嘛来了?
Ricky, what the hell you doing here?
有东西追我们,我不知道发生了什么
Something came after us...I don't know what happened
- 你说"有东西"是什么意思 - 我们一直跑到这里来
- What do you mean something...      - We ran all the way here
慢一点,什么东西追你们?
Slow down. What came after you?
- 我不知道 - 你们当时在哪儿?
- I don't know!      - Where were you?
我们在学校里,马克,他,他死了
We were at the school.  Mark...h-he's dead...
我想它们也杀了尼克
and I think they got Nick, too
是什么东西?
What was it?
瑞奇
Ricky!
我不知道
I don't know
打电话求助
Call in help
必须让什么人知道这些
Somebody's got to know about this
艾迪
Eddie
分派员,我们的支援呢?
Dispatch, where's that backup?
分派员,回答
Dispatch, come in
我们走,离开这个鬼地方
Let's go, let's get the hell out of here
凯瑞?
Carrie?
断电了
The power's out
凯瑞?
Carrie?
凯瑞,是你吗?
Carrie, are you over...
哦
Oh!
哦,天呐
Oh, my God
救命
Help me!
我们得一直跑,宝贝
We have to keep running, baby
离开这个鬼地方
Let's get outta here!
不,不,不
No, no! No!
妈妈,我们扔下了他
Mommy! We left him!
安静
Quiet. Shh
过来,过来
Come on, come on
妈妈,我害怕
Mommy, I'm scared
没事,没事,我们会没事的
Shh. It's okay. It's okay. We're gonna be okay
你见到了吗?
Did you see one?
我也是
Me, too
妈妈,你为什么要丢下爸爸?
Mommy, why did you leave Daddy?
让她闭嘴
Shut her up!
把烟掐灭,趴下
Hey. Put the cigarette out and get down
去你的,我可不藏在这等死
Fuck you. I'm not gonna die hiding
去你的
Fuck you
- 你会把我们害死的 - 我想回家
- You're gonna get us all killed      - I wanna go home!
- 让她闭嘴,让她闭嘴 - 我想找爸爸
- Shut her up. Shut her up      - I wanna see Daddy!
让她闭嘴,不然我向上帝发誓
Shut her the fuck up, or I swear to God...
我可不觉得警察局是个好主意
I don't think the police station is such a hot idea
你想让我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
我们不知道我们对付的是什么
We don't know what we're dealing with
快点
Come on
小心
Look out!
警长
Sheriff
- 达西? - 艾迪
- Darcy?      - Eddie
达西,怎么了,你在干什么?
Darcy, what happened? What are you doing?
- 厨房里,凯瑞的胃 - 什么?
- At the diner. Carrie's stomach      - What?
- 什么? - 到处都是血
- Shh. What?      - There was so much blood
她的胃,没了
Her stomach...it was gone
她死了,她死了
She's dead! She's dead...
瑞奇,把她扶进去
Ricky, get her inside
让她进去
Get her in
艾迪,不停地死人
Eddie, people are dying
我们需要枪
We need guns
国民警卫队很快就会过来
The National Guard'll be here soon
还不够快
Not soon enough
不敢相信我让你这样做
Can't believe I'd letting you do this
这个计划很蠢
This plan is stupid
我们得马上离开镇子
Let's just leave town now
因为我们没有武器
'Cause we're not going to make it out of town
就走不了,傻鸟
without weapons, dickhead
你说话太蠢了,戴尔,闭嘴
You're too stupid to talk, Dale. |Shut up
枪在哪儿?
Where are the guns?
跟着我
Follow me
在这里
Here they are
戴尔,找个袋子来
Dale, grab some bags
杰西,把枪上膛
Jesse, load them up
艾迪,你有电把那东西点亮?
Eddie, you got power on that thing?
是啊,我需要光
Yeah, I just need some light
走,走,走
Go! Go! Go!
第一小队,封锁这个区域
Ground One, secure the area
建立隔离带,掩护第二小队
Set up perimeter, provide cover for Ground Two
收到,零到六号出发
Roger, Zero-6 out
走,走,走
Move! Move! Move!
报告情况
Report status
第一小队已建好隔离带
Ground One has secured perimeter
第二小队已建好隔离带
Ground Two has secured perimeter
警长马若勒斯呼叫国民警卫队,请回答
This is Sheriff Morales for the National Guard. Come in
重复,警长马若勒斯呼叫国民警卫队
Repeat, Sheriff Morales for the National Guard
请回答
Come in
我是国民警卫队,89师
This is Lieutenant Woods, 89th Troop Command...
伍得中尉
Colorado National Guard
请讲,警长
Go ahead, Sheriff
你的位置在哪里,中尉,完毕
What's your location, Lieutenant? Over
我们在干道上
We're on Main Street
听着,中尉,我不知道
Listen, Lieutenant, I don't know
你们的人要面对什么
what your men are walking into...
但是我们的情况变得越来越糟糕
but our situation is getting worse
中尉,请回答,你还在吗?
Lieutenant, come in. Are you there?
我们有个人失踪了
We have a missing man
等一下,警长
Hold on, Sheriff
- 射击 - 我们遭遇了
- Fire!      - We've got contact!
- 停止射击 - 我们中埋伏了
- Hold your fire!      - It's a fucking ambush!
- 防御,九点钟
Fender, 9:00!
究竟是他妈的怎么回事?
What the hell's going on out there? !
我们遭遇了
We've got contact!
撤退,重复,撤退
Fall back! I repeat, fall back!
中尉
Lieutenant!
中尉,你在吗?
Lieutenant, are you there?
中尉,请回答,你在吗?
Lieutenant, come in. Are you there?
我们逃不了了,是吧?
We're not going to make it, are we?
别开枪,随便拿
Don't shoot! Take what you want!
我不该为了每小时六圆两角被杀
I'm not getting killed for no $6.25 an hour
我们被攻击了
We've been attacked
恐怖分子袭击吉那森了?
Terrorists hit Gunnison?
早告诉你他们有天会的
Told you they would one day
你们是什么人,喝高了?
What are you guys, stoned?
拿把枪
Grab some rifles
你看到那个了吗?
You see that?
快点,茉莉
Hurry up, Molly
Hurry, Molly
有人吗?
Hello? !
Hello?
你受伤了吗?
Are you hurt?
进来吧
Come on in
她在这儿会安全的
She'll be safe here
罗森医生请到2号急救室
Dr. Lossen to O.R. 2, stat
使劲压住伤口
Keep pressure on that
再来一升
Another liter
等一下
Hold up
明显的外伤
Apparently got a carotid
直接带他去急救室
Take him straight to Trauma
慢一点
Easy now
上来吧
Here you go
黄色警报,黄色警报
Code yellow, code yellow
所有非轮班医护人员马上到特别监护室报道
All non-shift medical personnel report to Critical Care
嗨
Hi
灯什么时候重新打开的?
When are the lights going back on?
在电源恢复之前,我们起用紧急发电机
We're on emergency generators until the power's restored
哦,上帝
Oh, God
哦,我想我的羊水破了
Oh, I think my water just broke
好的
Okay
我去找个医生
I'll find a doctor
不
No!
嘿
Hey
你们两个都在发抖
You two look pretty shaken up
今天晚上对她来说很不容易
Hasn't been an easy night for her
那你怎么样?
And what about you?
我会活着
I'll live
好吧
Okay
我们5分钟后出发
We're leaving in five minutes
谢谢你
Thank you
他在哪儿?
Where is he?
把枪给我,把枪给我
Give me the gun. Give me the gun!
跟我来
Come on!
妈妈
Mommy!
回去,是个陷阱
Turn back! It's a trap!
是陷阱,陷阱
It's a trap! It's a trap!
什么鬼玩意儿?
What the fuck?
- 跑,跑,跑 - 跑
- Go! Go! Go!      - Go!
茉莉,快点,跑,跑,茉莉
Molly, come on, run! Run, Molly!
所有人,跑,跑,到外面去
Everyone, go, go! Out the front!
操他妈的
Fuck this!
打死这狗日的
Shoot the fucking thing!
- 达拉斯 - 那是什么东西?
- Dallas...      - What was that thing?
怎么?
What...? !
这不可能
That's not possible
妈的
Shit
出问题了
Something's wrong
检查下其他房间
Check the other rooms!
怎么回事?
What is...?
- 快点,对 - 跑
- Come on, yeah...      - Go...
跑,孩子,跑,别停下
Go, baby, go! Keep running
一直往前,一直往前
Straight ahead. Straight ahead
发生了什么?
What the hell?
这就是我们的救援?
This is our help? !
出了什么鬼事,艾迪?
What the fuck is going on, Eddie? !
尸体都跑到哪儿去了?
Where the hell are the bodies?
哦,它们会把我们全杀了的
Oh, they're gonna kill us all!
我们还没死
We're not dead yet
也许还有武器和装备我们能用
There may be weapons and equipment we can still use
电台
Radio
国民警卫队,请回答
National Guard, come in
重复,国民警卫队,请回答
Repeat...any National Guard unit, come in
我是美国军队史迪文上校
This is Colonel Stevens, U.S. Army
表明你们的身份
Identify yourself
警长,艾迪·马若勒斯
Sheriff Eddie Morales
吉那森,罗拉多州
Gunnison, Colorado
你必须帮我们,上校
You have to help us, Colonel
这里有某种异形
There's some kind of infestation
如果我们不马上得到帮助,我们就都会死
and if we don't get help soon, there won't be any of us left
军队的疏散计划是什么?
What's the army's evacuation plan?
上校?
Colonel?
上校,我们需要立即疏散
Colonel, we need immediate evac
警长,所有的地面通道
Sheriff, all ground routes
都不安全
have been compromised
30分钟之后,吉莉安广场
There is an airlift in 30 minutes
会有一次空中救援
from Gilliam Circle
确认:,空中救援,吉莉安广场
Confirm: airlift, Gilliam Circle
我们20分钟后到达
We'll be there in 20 minutes
但那是在市中心
But that's right in the center of town
我们会赶到的,上校
We'll be there, Colonel
你是什么鬼玩意儿?
What the fuck are you?
所有人,到车厢里去
Everyone, get in the Striker!
我来开车
I'll drive
上车,快,快,快
Get up, go, go, go, go
你确定你能开这玩意儿?
You sure you can drive that thing?
好吧,我来负责拿枪
All right, I'll get on the gun
别打偏
Don't miss
别撞车
Don't crash
抓紧了
Hold on!
为什么停下来?
Why are we stopping?
这没一点道理
It doesn't make any sense
吉莉安广场在小镇的正中央
Gilliam Circle is right in the center of town
我们会被那些东西包围的
We'll be surrounded by those things
- 等下,你在说什么? - 我认为上校在骗我们
- Wait a second...what are you saying?      - I think the colonel was lying
真荒谬
That's crazy
政府从来不对人民撒谎
The government doesn't lie to people
军队会首先考虑污染
The army thinks about containment first
他们不能冒险让情况变得更糟糕
They can't risk this getting any worse
救援就在几公里以外的地方,他们正在等我们
Help is a few miles down that road and they're waiting for us
如果你不想带我们去,我带
Now, if you won't drive us there, I will
艾迪,如果她是对的
Eddie, if she's right, the only thing
等着我们的就是更多的异形
down that road are more of those things
你没有认真考虑这件事
You're not seriously considering this
我考虑如何让我们活下去
I'm considering whatever keeps us alive
就是逃出这个镇子
Which means getting out of this town
镇里只有两架直升机
There are only two helicopters in town...
但一架在机场
but one's at the airport
不,太远了,我们不可能到那儿
No, it's too far. We'll never make it
另一架在医院
The other one's at the hospital
医院的人可能用它逃生了
The people at the hospital probably used it to get out
但那是我们的机会
That's a chance we have to take
如果你们错了,直升机飞走了
If you're wrong and the helicopter's gone...
我们就都死了
we're all dead
如果我对了,他们跟着你,也是死路一条
If I'm right, they're dead if they follow you
有辆卡车开过来了
There's a truck coming
在吉莉安广场
There will be
将会有紧急疏散
an emergency evacuation from Gilliam Circle
医疗救护和空中救援
Medical care and airlift...
警长,你在这儿干什么?
Sheriff, what the hell are you doing in there?
别操心这个了
Never mind that
你们要去空中救援点?
You guys heading to the airlift?
是的
Yeah
好,跟着我们,没多少时间了
Okay, follow us. We don't have much time
好了,听着
All right, listen up
每个人都必须马上做出决定
Everybody's got to choose right now
我们乘坦克,去医院
I'm going to the hospital with the tank
我们只需要跑到镇中心
We all need to go to the center of town
- 没错 - 我跟着我哥哥
- That's right      - I'm going with my brother
- 我和你一起 - 我进坦克去
- I'm with you      - I'm going in the tank
达拉斯,别这么做
Dallas, don't do this
她错了
She's wrong
不管是不是兄弟,他错了
And brother or not, he's wrong
你会害死他们的
You're gonna get them killed!
我们没时间了,警长,我们必须马上出发
We're running out of time, Sheriff...we gotta move now
等下
Hold on!
我们跟你一起去
We're coming with you!
等等
Wait
保重
Take care
我希望我们都错了
I hope we're both wrong
医疗救护和空中救援
Medical care and airlift...
出发
Let's go!
在吉莉安广场
There will be an emergency evacuation
将会有紧急疏散
from Gilliam Circle
医疗救护和空中救援,提供给所有居民
Medical care and airlift will be provided for all residents
我没有救任何人
I didn't help anybody
我太害怕了
I was too scared
我就看着他们死
I just watched them die
好了,穿上这个
All right, put these on
你也是
You, too
好了,听着
All right, listen...
不管在里面发生什么事
whatever happens inside...
唯一不能受伤的是凯莉,明白吗?
the only person that can't get hurt is Kelly, all right?
我们都保护凯莉
We all protect Kelly
这是哪出,泰坦尼克?
What is this, the Titanic?
去他妈的妇女孩子先走那一套,伙计
Screw the women and children first shit, man
听着,白痴,除非你会开直升机
Look, asshole, unless you can fly the helicopter...
不然就闭嘴,我们走
shut the fuck up. Let's go
哦,天呐
Oh, Jesus
也许他们都走了
Maybe they've all gone
哦,上帝,不
Oh, God, no!
打死他妈的
Fucking shoot it!
杰西,不,等等
Jesse, no, wait!
跑,快
Move, now!
杰西
Jesse!
不,等等
No, wait!
瑞奇
Ricky!
瑞奇,等等
Ricky, wait!
狗娘养的
Motherfucker!
瑞奇
Ricky!
走吧
Come on
快点,起来
Come on, get up
你不会死的
You're gonna make it
我们得马上走,现在
We have to go...now!
来
Come on...
快点
Come on!
走,走,走,走,走
Go! Go, go, go, go!
乔
Joe!
所有人都在吗?
Is this everybody?
这是所有活着的人
This is all that's left
你听到了什么?
What have you heard?
空中救援马上就到
The airlift will be here soon
安全
Clear!
跟上
Come on!
走,走,你没事吧?
Go, go! You all right?
过来,茉莉
Come here, Molly
跑,跑,跟着你妈
Go! Go! Follow your mom!
快点
Come on!
所有人,快点
Everyone, move!
跑,茉莉
Run, Molly!
快点
Come on!
达拉斯
Dallas!
我在试
I'm trying!
你打算用那东西?
Are you gonna shoot that thing?
等一等
Hang on!
我们走
Let's go!
抱稳她了?
You got her?
卧倒
Get down!
史迪文上校,这里是吉那森镇
Colonel Stevens, this is Gunnison County
请求疏散,完毕
requesting status on evac! Over!
上校,空中救援在哪儿?
Colonel, where's the airlift?
警长,我们还有10公里
Sheriff, we are ten miles out
原地待命,完毕
Hold your position. Over
上校,我们在这里,完毕
Colonel, we're here. Over
上帝拯救我们
God help us all
好了,离开这儿,马上
All right, get out of here...now
我来争取点时间
I'm gonna buy us some time
我不离开你
I'm not leaving you
上直升机
Get to the chopper!
你不必这样做,达拉斯
You don't have to do this, Dallas
马上,去,去
Now! Go! Go!
放马过来,狗娘养的
Come on, you motherfuckers!
好,走
Okay, go!
凯莉,趴下
Kelly! Get down!
走,走,走
Go! Go! Go!
嘿,这边
Hey, over here!
快点
Come on
好了,走
Okay, go!
操
Fuck!
嘿,你过来
Hey, come on over here!
快点
Come on!
干你娘的
Fuck you!
我们不能丢下他不管
We're not leaving without him!
我们必须得走
We have to go
他会赶来的
He'll make it!
死
Die...!
出发
Let's go!
妈妈?
Mommy?
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes!
- 抓紧 - 妈妈
- Hang on!      - Mommy!
达拉斯?
Dallas?
哦,天呐
Oh,Jesus
嘿,你还好吧? 瑞奇?
Hey, you all right? Ricky?
使劲按,甜心
- Yeah      - Press harder, honey
放下武器
Drop your weapons!
你们这群王八蛋杀了整个镇子的人
You bastards killed the entire town
我们只是服从命令
We're just following orders
放下武器
Now, put down your weapons
我弟弟需要救护
We need a medic for my brother
救援马上就到
Medevac is inbound
收集所有武器,建立隔离带
Secure any weapons, and let's set up a perimeter!
出发,快点
Let's go! Move it!
我想我跟你说过别撞车
Thought I told you not to crash
妈妈?
Mommy?
怪物都死了吗?
Are the monsters gone?
都死了
They're gone
这个世界还没准备好接受这种武器
The world isn't ready for this technology
但这不是给我们的世界准备的,不是吗,尤塔尼女士?
But this isn't for our world, is it, Ms. Yutani?